Pesology     

* * *

### Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Collect Call, LLC d/b/a Pesology ("Pesology") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its Website (each, a "User"). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you about what kinds of information we, at Pesology, may gather about you, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Pesology does not own or control, or to people that Pesology does not employ or manage. This includes any companies from whom you may have ordered services or products that are transmitted over Pesology's mobile or billing platform, and any companies from whom you may be purchasing other services.

#### Privacy

Pesology is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Pesology. This Website is not directed at children under 18 years of age.

#### Collected Information

Pesology may collect various types of personal information including name, mobile telephone number, address, zip code, billing information, that, either alone or in combination with other kinds of information, may personally identify Users. Pesology may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information.

#### Mobile-Specific Information We Collect

Most of the personally identifying information we collect is what you tell us about yourself. For example, certain of our products and services allow you to interact and share personal information and data with others. You choose what you want to share and how you want to share it.

Sometimes, we record your phone number. We record your phone number when you send it to us; ask us to remember it; or make a call or send a text message or Short Message Service (SMS) to or from Pesology. If you ask us to remember your phone number, we will associate your phone number with your account ID based on your device and hardware IDs; so if you change your device or hardware, you will have to re-associate this new device or hardware with your account before we can authenticate you.

Most of the other information we collect for mobile, such as your device and hardware IDs and device type, the request type, your carrier, your carrier user ID, the content of your request, and basic usage stats about your device and use of Pesology's products and services does not by itself identify you to Pesology, though it may be unique or consist of or contain information that you consider personal.

Certain of our products and services allow you to download and/or personalize the content you receive from us. For these products and services, we will record information about your downloads and preferences, along with any information you provide yourself.

For products and services with voice recognition capabilities, we collect and store a copy of the voice commands you make to the product or service. To improve processing of your voice commands, we may also continuously record in temporary memory a few seconds of ambient background noise. This recording stays only temporarily on the device and is not sent to Pesology.

### Location Services

Please refer to the following link:

##### Cookies

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do \[do not\] link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. \[IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to \[describe the purpose for which you do this\]

We use a third-party tracking service Google Analytics that uses scripts to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate \[state what information is captured, e.g., usage and volume statistics\] to \[state purpose of the collection\]

Cookies are files that web browsers place on a computer's hard drive and are used to tell us whether customers and visitors have visited the site previously. Our site uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the system to uniquely identify you while you are logged in. This information allows us to process your online data and requests.

Session cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you have logged in. We use persistent cookies, which only we can read and use, to identify the fact that you are a Pesology customer or prior site visitor. Users who disable their browser's ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Pesology Website but may not be able to successfully use certain enhanced features.

#### How We Use Information

 Pesology may use personally identifiable information collected through our Website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Pesology and its trusted affiliates independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with Pesology and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. , If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at support.Pesology.com.

Pesology may also use information collected through our Website for research regarding the effectiveness of the Website and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Pesology, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. Because Pesology is a global company, we may share your information with other Pesology affiliates, business units or contractors in other parts of the world, who will maintain the privacy of your information in accordance with this policy.

Pesology may also use information for fulfillment of user requests, to contact users or for reporting purposes. We limit access to your personally identifiable information to employees and contractors who we believe need access in order to provide services to you or to do their jobs. You should know that your personally identifiable information may be transferred from your home country to employees and contractors in other areas of the world, who may communicate with you regarding your inquiry.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@Pesology.com

#### Disclosure of Information

Pesology may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners.

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

If Pesology is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@pesology.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@Pesology.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Privacy Inquiries**

If you have questions or concerns about our policies concerning privacy, data collection, data processing or data transmission, please email us at [info@pesology.com](mailto:info@pesology.com), or write us at 75 N. Woodard Avenue, Suite 82503, Tallahassee, FL 32313

**
